1。
1。
Come on, Tang Wenqi.
تعال ، تانغ وينكي.
It's such a great opportunity,
إنها فرصة عظيمة ،
Kiss her.
قبلها.
Darts.
نبلات.
You want to play this?
تريد أن تلعب هذا؟
When I was a park killer,
عندما كنت قاتل حديقة ،
the stall owners saw me,
رآني أصحاب الأكشاك ،
There's nothing I'm not afraid of.
لا يوجد شيء لست خائفًا منه.
The park is.
الحديقة.
Stop asking and pay for it.
توقف عن السؤال وادفع ثمنها.
All right,
حسنًا،
boss. Five rounds,
رئيس.  خمس جولات ،
Okay,
تمام،
Here,
هنا،
Good for you, young man.
جيد لك أيها الشاب.
After marrying such a great wife,
بعد الزواج من هذه الزوجة العظيمة ،
You'll be lucky for the rest of your life.
ستكون محظوظًا لبقية حياتك.
No, I'm not.
لا أنا لست كذلك.
Boss,
رئيس،
thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Five more rounds.
خمس جولات أخرى.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
Come on.
تعال.
Let's play.
هيّا بنا لنلعب.
He's even a park killer.
إنه حتى قاتل حديقة.
I think you're the boss's God of Wealth.
أعتقد أنك إله الثروة للرئيس.
Are you done?
هل انتهيت؟
I'll pay you back.
سأعيد لك ما دفعته.
That's not necessary.
هذا ليس ضروريا.
Just tell me what gift you want next time.
فقط قل لي ما هي الهدية التي تريدها في المرة القادمة.
I'll just buy one for you.
سأشتري واحدة فقط من أجلك.
Why bother?
لماذا تهتم؟
How do you know I like that hairpin?
كيف تعرف أنني أحب دبوس الشعر هذا؟
How can I not know that you've seen through it?
كيف لا أعرف أنك رأيت من خلالها؟
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
I must practice darts hard next time.
يجب أن أمارس لعبة السهام بقوة في المرة القادمة.
Win it back.
استردها.
Watch out!
احترس!
I'm
أنا
so sorry,
اسف جدا،
I drank too much yesterday,
شربت كثيرا البارحة
but I haven't recovered yet,
لكني لم أتعافى بعد ،
Why did you come out if you didn't recover?
لماذا خرجت إذا لم تتعافى؟
I have to come.
لدي القادمة.
I'm not coming. Didn't you go to see
أنا لست قادما.  لم تذهب لترى
some pretty man's show?
عرض بعض الرجل الجميل؟
What kind of handsome man is there?
أي نوع من الرجل الوسيم هناك؟
Besides,
بجانب،
what does a handsome man have to do with you?
ما علاقة الرجل الوسيم بك؟
Why is it none of my business?
لماذا هو ليس من أعمالي؟
You're mine.
أنت لي.
Your what?
ما بك؟
You can't say it, can you?
لا يمكنك قول ذلك ، أليس كذلك؟
You're mine.
أنت لي.
Oh no.
أوه لا.
He's good at it.
إنه جيد في ذلك.
He's not going to kiss me, is he?
لن يقبلني ، أليس كذلك؟
Good roommate,
رفيق سكن جيد ،
go away!
يبتعد!
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
لا أريد التحدث معك بعد الآن.
Don't talk to me.
لا تتحدث معي.
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
You're not looking for Lingxiu, are you?
أنت لا تبحث عن Lingxiu ، أليس كذلك؟
Can't you tell they did it on purpose?
ألا يمكنك أن تخبرهم أنهم فعلوا ذلك عن قصد؟
Where am I going?
إلى أين أنا ذاهب؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I'll take you to a nice place.
سآخذك إلى مكان جميل.
This is the good place you mentioned?
هذا هو المكان الجيد الذي ذكرته؟
I've prepared everything.
لقد جهزت كل شيء.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
when I first met the woman in Tsing Yi,
عندما قابلت المرأة لأول مرة في تسينغ يي ،
I've made up my mind.
أنا إتخذت قراري.
Let her see the most beautiful fireworks in the world.
دعها ترى أجمل الألعاب النارية في العالم.
So you studied gunpowder,
لذلك درست البارود ،
for fireworks.
للألعاب النارية.
Yeah,
نعم،
I thought,
اعتقدت،
Look at that,
انظر إلى ذلك ،
Three,
ثلاثة،
Two,
اثنين،
One.
واحد.
It's so pretty.
انها جميلة جدا.
So pretty.
جميل جدا.
Oh, right.
صحيح.
This is for you.
هذا لك.
Isn't this the hairpin just now?
أليس هذا هو دبوس الشعر الآن؟
That's right.
صحيح.
Don't you want it?
ألا تريده؟
You didn't pay for it, did you?
أنت لم تدفع ثمنها ، أليس كذلك؟
How is that possible?
كيف يعقل ذلك؟
I won this with my own hands, okay?
لقد ربحت هذا بيدي ، حسنًا؟
You are me.
انت انا.
-It's you. -What is your
-انه انت.  -ما هو ك
good roommate?
رفيق سكن جيد؟
You're the girl I like.
أنت الفتاة التي أحبها.
Wu...
وو ...
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
Lingxiu,
Lingxiu ،
let me do it.
دعني افعلها.
Don't tire you out.
لا تتعبك.
Didn't you just say that?
ألم تقل ذلك للتو؟
Our husband and wife are united,
زوجنا وزوجتنا متحدان ،
and our profits are cut off.
وأرباحنا مقطوعة.
Husband and wife,
زوج و زوجة،
wait.
انتظر.
we,
نحن،
Husband and wife,
زوج و زوجة،
all right,
حسنًا،
Sprinkle the petals.
رش البتلات.
Okay, okay.
حسنا حسنا.
Husband and wife,
زوج و زوجة،
Husband and wife.
زوج و زوجة.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
why are there petals here?
لماذا توجد بتلات هنا؟
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
This kind of campus love is so dreamy.
هذا النوع من الحب في الحرم الجامعي حالم جدًا.
Are you all right, Brother Wu?
هل أنت بخير يا أخي وو؟
You're blushing,
أنت تحمر خجلاً ،
How about I ask Lingxiu to show it to you?
ماذا لو طلبت من Lingxiu أن تظهر لك ذلك؟
No, no, no.
لا لا لا.
I'll just go out and get some fresh air.
سأخرج فقط وأخذ بعض الهواء النقي.
Why are you dressed like this?
لماذا ترتدي مثل هذا؟
Is this something I can read without spending money on?
هل هذا شيء يمكنني قراءته دون إنفاق المال عليه؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Let me have a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة.
Chestnut wants to see you. Go
كستناء يريد رؤيتك.  يذهب
and have a look.
وإلقاء نظرة.
What can he do for me?
ماذا يمكنه أن يفعل من أجلي؟
Don't rush to get dressed.
لا تتسرع في ارتداء ملابسك.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
I don't know what kind of stimulation she suffered.
لا أعرف نوع التحفيز الذي عانت منه.
Love always hurts.
الحب يؤلم دائما.
Don't talk nonsense.
لا تتحدث عن هراء.
My Lady,
سيدتي،
I finally found you.
أخيرا وجدتك.
What's the matter? Why are you in such a hurry?
ماذا جرى؟  لماذا أنت في عجلة من أمرك؟
General,
عام،
you're here. What?
أنت هنا.  ماذا؟
Oh no.
أوه لا.
I'm really done for today.
لقد انتهيت حقًا لهذا اليوم.